Thomas Jackson

Graphics & Games Programmer

E-mail: Tom.Jackson1711@gmail.com

Phone: +44 (0) 7494092928

Portfolio: https://tomizzed2001.github.io

A confident and dedicated individual with a wide range of communication, technical, and critical thinking skills. Excels in teamwork both as a leader and team member to provide valuable contributions to the task at hand. A logical minded, creative student who puts to use a combination of learnt knowledge and experience to efficiently produce quality work.

Technical Skills

Programming Languages Development Tools Graphics APIs Experienced In

C/C++

C#

GLSL

Python

Java

Unreal 5 /4

Unity

RenderDoc

Git

Vulkan **Physics**

OpenGL Rendering

Mesh Optimisation

Employment History

CLO Coffee - Roastery & Café

Leeds, UK Jul 2023 – Mar 2024

Café Operator

Organising a small team of people to efficiently operate the café.

- Solving customer complaints and or queries in a timely manner.
- Engaging in meaningful conversation with regular and new customers.
- Communicating with café management to ensure stock levels were maintained.

Nandos Leeds / York, UK Front of House Staff Jun 2019 - May 2023

- Greeting and interacting with customers during their dining experience.
- Working as part of a team to assure customer satisfaction.
- Managing time effectively to maximise customer turnover during busy periods.
- 4-time employee of the month nominee and 2-time winner.

Education

University of Leeds Leeds, UK Sep 2023 - Sep 2024

MSc in High Performance Graphics & Games Engineering

Distinction

Relevant Modules: Animation and Simulation, Geometric Processing, Rendering, High Performance Graphics,

Dissertation: Marching Cubes for Low-Poly Mesh Generation

University of York York, UK

BEng in Computer Science

Sep 2020 – Jun 2023

First Class Honours

Relevant Modules: Object-Oriented Programming, Software Engineering, High Performance Computing

Dissertation: Washed Up: A 2D Survival and Tower Defence Game in Unity

Garforth Academy Leeds, UK Sep 2018 - Jun 2020

A-Level Mathematics - Grade A A-Level Physics - Grade A

A-Level Computer Science - Grade A

Hobbies & Interests

During my free time I enjoy creating my own games and playing the latest PC games, especially the survival ones! I also love to participate in Esports events, having represented York University during my time there, both as a player and an organiser; it's something I really like to keep up with. Away from my computer, I'm passionate about exploring the British countryside and often go walking and cycling on scenic routes. When opportunity arises, I'm also a hobbyist fossil hunter on the Yorkshire Coast and love showing off my collection.